Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
- Series III. Empty Closet
  - Back Issues on Microfilm
    - Empty Closet, September 1984 - March 1989 (Reel 3)
    - Empty Closet, April 1989 - September 1992 (Reel 4)
    - Empty Closet, October 1992 - June 1995 (Reel 5)
    - Empty Closet, July 1995 - September 1997 (Reel 6)
    - Empty Closet, October 1997 - January 2000 (Reel 7)
    - Empty Closet, February 2000 - April 2002 (Reel 8)
    - Empty Closet, May 2002 - May 2004 (Reel 9)
    - Empty Closet, June 2004 - April 2006 (Reel 10)
    - Empty Closet, May 2006 - April 2008 (Reel 11)
    - Empty Closet, May 2008 - February 2010 (Reel 12)
    - Empty Closet, February 2004 - May 2004 (Reel 13)
  - Digital copies of Empty Closet, 1971-2010
    - Empty Closet, 1971-2010; HD-9
    - Empty Closet and records surveyed, 2010-04-2011-08; HD-8
- Series IV. Ephemera and Memorabilia
  - Clothing
    All are T-shirts unless otherwise noted.
    - International Mr. Leather, Chicago, 1997; MU-2142 (Box 28)
      Tank top
    - International Mr. Leather, 1997; MU-2043 (Box 28)
    - 19th Ward, Undated; MU-2144 (Box 28)
    - Stonewall 25, 1994; MU-2145 (Box 28)
    - San Francisco, Undated; MU-2146 (Box 28)
      With image of pink triangle
    - Canadian Human Rights Campaign, Undated; MU-2147 (Box 28)
      "Working at the Front of the Shop"
    - March on Washington, 1993; MU-2148 (Box 28)
    - Rainbow Visa Card, Undated; MU-2149 (Box 28)
      "The power of one"
    - National Coming Out Day, Undated; MU-2150 (Box 28)
    - International Display of the Entire NAMES Project AIDS memorial quilt, 1992; MU-2151 (Box 28)
    - Hawaii Equal Rights Marriage Project, Undated; MU-2152 (Box 28)
    - Helping People with AIDS - Rochester, NY, Undated; MU-2153 (Box 28)
    - International Mr. Leather, Chicago, 1996; MU-2154 (Box 28)
    - San Francisco, Undated; MU-2155 (Box 28)
    - Chicago Eagle, Undated; MU-2156 (Box 28)
    - The Names Project, Undated; MU-2157 (Box 28)
      Sweatshirt
    - AIDS Walk Atlanta, 1994; MU-2158 (Box 28)
    - Leather Chicago, 1995; MU-2159 (Box 29)
    - W.E. - We're Everywhere, Undated; MU-2160 (Box 29)
    - International Mr. Leather, 1996; MU-2161 (Box 29)
    - Galaxe (Gays and Lesbians at Xerox), Undated; MU-2162 (Box 29)
    - 5375 Picnic, 1997; MU-2163 (Box 29)
    - Picnic Fest, Rochester, NY, 1989; MU-2164 (Box 29)
    - Gay Games IV, 1994; MU-2165 (Box 29)
    - Names Project Memorial Quilt, 1996; MU-2166 (Box 29)
    - Warsaw, South Beach, Undated; MU-2167 (Box 29)
    - The Names Project, Undated; MU-2168 (Box 29)
    - Pride and Company of San Francisco, Undated; MU-2169 (Box 29)
    - Olympic Summer Games, Atlanta, GA, 1996; MU-2170 (Box 29)
    - None of us can go it alone, Undated; MU-2171 (Box 29)
    - Rochester Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival, Undated; MU-2172 (Box 29)
    - Gay, Lesbian and Straight Education Network - Equality March in Washington D.C. T-shirt, October 2009; MU-2195 (Box 29)
    - Aids Walk Genesee Valley T-shirt, 2010; MU-2196 (Box 29)
      Gift of Sean Soper
    - Rochester Victory Alliance T-shirt, undated; MU-2197 (Box 29)
    - GAGV Rochester Pride T-shirt, 2010; MU-2198 (Box 29)
    - GALAXE T-shirt, undated; MU-2199 (Box 29)
    - I Love Pride, 2011; MU-2173 (Box 30)
    - Youth Pride, 2011; MU-2174 (Box 30)
    - Skull and Cross Bones, Undated; MU-2175 (Box 30)
    - March on Washington, 1993; MU-2204 (Box 30)
    - Names Project Memorial Quilt, Undated; MU-2205 (Box 30)
    - Rochester Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival, 1994; MU-2206 (Box 30)
    - Rochester Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival, 1995; MU-2207 (Box 30)
    - Rainbow Pride Connection - LGBT Conference, 2009; MU-2208 (Box 30)
    - Holly Near "Don't Hold Back", Undated; MU-2209 (Box 30)
    - Rochester Victory Alliance, Undated; MU-2210 (Box 30)
    - Womyn's Motorcycle Festival - 10 Year Anniversary, 1994; MU-2211 (Box 30)
    - "I can't even think straight", Undated; MU-2212 (Box 30)
    - Boston and New York AIDS Ride, Undated; MU-2213 (Box 30)
    - "Read My Lips", Undated; MU-2214 (Box 30)
    - 12th Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 1987; MU-2215 (Box 30)
    - Dyke March - San Francisco, 1996; MU-2216 (Box 30)
    - Pony Express Tour - Riding for Breast Cancer Research, 1996; MU-2217 (Box 30)
    - NERP Blue Scrubs, 2012; MU-2176 (Box 30)
    - PFLAG - Port Townsand, Undated; MU-2273 (Box 30)
      Originally located with Todd Plank materials
    - The Empty Closet, Undated; MU-2274 (Box 30)
    - Mains for Mayor, 2005; MU-2275 (Box 30)
    - Rochester Victory Alliance bag, Undated; MU-2182 (Box 30)
  - Pins and other Memorabilia
    - Queers in History software with booklet, c. 1993-1996; FD-21a (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Queers in History software with booklet, c. 1993-1996; FD-21b (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Metal box with business cards, Undated; MU-2177 (Box 31)
    - Muther's GAGV Pride mug, 1997; MU-2178 (Box 31)
    - 3 RuPaul coasters, 2010; MU-2180 (Box 31)
    - 2 coasters from the "Gear Up" safe sex campaign, Undated; MU-2181 (Box 31)
    - Together Proud and Strong, 1993; TR-10512 (Box 31)
      Recording made for 1993 March on Washington
    - "Out Spoken" magnet, Undated; MU-2278 (Box 31)
      Possibly from the RIT/NTID LGBT and Ally group
    - GAGV pin, Undated; MU-2183 (Box 32)
    - "I'd rather be gay in Rochester" pin, Undated; MU-2184 (Box 32)
    - GLBTQ Online Hight School magnet, Undated; MU-2218 (Box 32)
    - The Names Project pin, Undated; MU-2219 (Box 32)
    - Mains Volunteer pin, Undated; MU-2220 (Box 32)
    - Dignity-Integrity pin, Undated; MU-2221 (Box 32)
    - GAGV Anti-violence whistle and key chain, Undated; MU-2222 (Box 32)
    - Hope Takes Action yo-yo, undated; MU-2223 (Box 32)
    - PFLAG pin, Undated; MU-2224 (Box 32)
    - GAGV youth pin, Undated; MU-2290 (Box 32)
    - GAGV "Youth ROC!" pin, Undated; MU-2291 (Box 32)
    - GAGV "Here. Queer. All Year" pin, Undated; MU-2292 (Box 32)
    - Women's MC Festival pins (4), 1985, 1990, 1992, 1994; MU-2293-2296 (Box 32)
    - Gay Lesbian Vote 88 pin, 1988; MU-2297 (Box 32)
    - WMF Pony Express Tour pin, 1996; MU-2298 (Box 32)
    - Lesbian and Gay Values are American Values - Pride Vote 96 pin, 1996; MU-2299 (Box 32)
    - Unknown pins (2), 1992-1993; MU-2300-2301 (Box 32)
    - GAGV 30th Anniversary pin (2), 2003; MU-2302-2303 (Box 32)
    - Gay Rights Scrapbook, 1967-2006 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Awards and Certificates
    - Presidential Proclamation for Pride Month, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - State of New York Awards and Certificates, 1989, 1995, 2008-2008 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - County and City Awards and Certificates, 1988-1995, 2003, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - GAGV Awards, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Rochester Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Pride Parade plaque, 1991; MU-2277 (Box 31)
    - Perot Productions Award for Excellence plaque, 2003; MU-2276 (Box 31)
    - New York State Victim Assistance Academy Certificate, 2009-06 (Box 67, Folder 29)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Publications Removed From Collection 7560 - To Be Cataloged As Individual Serials In The Human Sexuality Collection. Multiple but unspecified issues are marked with (number of issues).
5th Freedom. May, July 1982.
The Advocate. Issue 354.
After Dark. v.4 no.7.
Albatross. (2)
Alternative. v.1 no.1.
ArtVoice. v.10 no.31.
Bay Windows. v.2 no.1.
The Beast. Issue 110.
Because We Care. (No issue number).
BGA Gayzette. Winter 1977-78, Winter 1979.
Big Apple Dyke News. Feb. 1982.
Body Politic. no.85-86.
Bondings (New Ways Ministry). Spring 1982.
Capitol Hill. v.4 no.2.
Chicago Gay Life. v.7 no.49, v.8 no.9-10.
Christopher Street. v.2 no.12.
City Newspaper. (Rochester City Newspaper) v.12 no.47; v.13 no.25; v.19 no.43; v.37 no.2, 24, 43; v.38 no.44; v.39 no.44.
City Pages. v.31 Issue 1593.
Community. v.2 no:1-2, no.11.
Connection. v.3 no.6-7.
The Empty Closet. nos. 110, 122, 126, 130, 132.
Equal Times. v.8 no.162.
Female FYI. August 1998, Issue 60.
Feminist Connection. v.3 no.10.
First Things First. September 1973.
Focus. July/Aug. 1981, July/Aug. 1982.
Focus Point. v.6 no.10, Issue 218.
The Front Page (Carolinas). v.3 no.6, 8.
The Furies. v.1; v.1 Issue 3, v.11 Issue 2.
Gay Community News. v.10 no.36; v.10 no.12, 17; v.10 no.28, 31, 37-38, 40, 46, 49; v.11 no.1-2, 4-5, 26.
GayLife (Chicago). v.8 no.1, 3.
Gay Morning. (6)
Gay News (Philadelphia). v.6 no.23; v.7 no.19, 22, 33-34, 36-39.
The Gay Paper. v.4 no.3-4.
Gay Post. #9
Gay Synagogue News. March, May 1982.
Gaze (Memphis). v.3 no.9.
Gertrude Stein Democratic Club Newsletter. v.2 no.5, 7.
Giovanni's Room. Winter 1982-1983.
GO Info. v.2 no.2-5.
Grass Roots. v.2 no.6; v.3 no.2; April 1975.
Icon. Summer 1998.
Impact (Louisiana). v.5 no.5.
Insider. v.6 no.29.
Interchange. v.2 no.2.
International Justice Monthly. v.2 no.2-6.
In Unity. v.6 no.3. Sept./Oct. 1980, Jan.1982.
Join Hands. Issue 2.
Kater Street. 1981:Oct., Dec., 1982:Feb., Apr.-July
Ladyslipper. 1983.
Lesbian Connection.. v.6 Issue 2.
Lesbian Connection Winter Catalog.. 1982-1983.
The Lesbian Feminist. March 1978, June 1982.
Lesbian Herstory Archives News. no.7.
Lesbian News. v.7 no.9-11.
Lesbian Rising. December 1977
Maine Gay Task Force Newsletter. v.1 no.4; v.2 no.1-2 (2 issues - February and March), v.2 no.4.
Maine Lesbian Feminist Newsletter. Aug. 1982.
Majority Report. v.2 no.8, 10; v.3 no.8, 10-12; v.4 no.1, 10, 12, 16; v.7 no.19.
Matrix: Women's Newsmagazine. Feb. 1982.
MOHR Information. (3)
Moonstorm. No.26-27.
More Light Update. v.2 no.12 resources, v.3 no.2.
News of the Columbus Gay and Lesbian Community. v.5 no.2-4, 6, 8.
New Women's Times. v.3 no.6; v.4 no.2-3v.9 no.3-5
New Women's Times Feminist Review. no. 26-27
New York Civil Liberties. v.30 no.3.
Northeast Alive. v.1 no.8, v.3 no.2.
Off Our Backs. v. 3 no. 5, 7-8, 10, 12; v. 4 no. 1-4, 8; v.12 no.6-7.
Oregon Gay Rights Report. v.8 no.2.
Our Own Community Press. v.6 no.6.
Out and About. No. 63-64, 66.
Outcome. No numbers. 5 issues.
Out Front. v.7 no.7.
OUT Pittsburgh. No.63, 66.
Pacific Exchange. v.1 no.1.
Parents FLAG. No. 1-3.
Plexus. v.8 no.6, v.9 no.2, 8.
PLGTF Bulleting. v.3 no.8..
Proceedings of the Triangle Area Gay Scientists. v.4 no.6.
Puce Mongoose. #64, 87, 89.
RFD (Roseburg Faggots and Dykes).. nos. 12-13, 26, 35.
San Francisco Bay Times. v.19 no.25.
San Francisco Spectrum. v.1 no.5.
Sisters United. v.20 no.16, 21.
Susan Saxe Defense Committee Newsletter. no. 2.
Task Force Report. v.8 no.5, v.9 no.1, 3-4.
This Way Out. v.5 no.2.
Tips and Tactics. v.3 no.1-4; v.4 no. 2-3; v.5 no.1
Together Gay. #2.
The Traveler. v.27 no.3
TWN. v.5 no.37, 40, 51, v.6 no.10
Vegas Gay Times. Issues 14.
Volume. April 15, 1994.
Washington Blade. (3)
The West Sider. July, Oct. 1976.
Women. v. 2 no. 2; v. 8 no. 3